[{"answer": "Well, what I would say, first of all, Piers, is thank you so much for having me tonight.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "I mean you guys are in the White House, aren't you?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "I feel very disappointed that there hasn't been more inroad into those jobless figures.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Do you feel disappointed that there's been no greater inroad into those jobless figures?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Don't start something now, Piers.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "If you're doing so well there, maybe you should be in the White House, have you thought of that?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, as you know, of course, Barack Obama voted against raising the debt ceiling when he was a senator and is now playing politics from the other side claiming that you're supposed to do this to give the president the money he wants.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "I mean isn't it a bit frankly hypocritical to be throwing the toys out of the prime now and said the Democrats can't do it given how often the Republicans have done it?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Well, again, you just asked about a number and I said of the cost of the Afghan war, I mean the whole Afghan war today cost $120 billion.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "I mean what percentage of blame, as we stand here today, should be apportioned to Republican decision making?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "I'm trying to give you a percentage of -- for instance the Afghan war, two-thirds of the cost there this year was put in by Obama.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Why are you avoiding my question?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Are you not remembering that Barack Obama campaigned for president on the idea that the Afghan war was the right war, that he was for all of that, and you want to explain --", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Wasn't it?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "But you're asking for a partisan blame to be apportioned here, right?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Look, you want to argue why Medicare and Medicaid are going bankrupt, those were created by Democrats.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "And so when you actually analyze exactly the percentage blame, and that's why I've been trying to get you to put a percentage on it, it's just quite an interesting exercise, isn't it?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Why don't we --", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Do you want to go back to that and play partisan politics?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "I started this conversation discussing that Bush spent too much money or allowed too much money to be spent during his presidency.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "And that kind of partisan opinion is what is preventing any kind of sensible deal, a strategy being achieved, isn't it?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "They should.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "And the politicians should just sort this mess out, shouldn't they?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "I'm doing great.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Mr. Mayor, how are you?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "Well, I can't say that I know the hearts and minds of the Congress people in our -- in the federal government.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "I mean in your experience of these things, how much of what's going on right now in terms of this impasse between Republicans and Democrats is political and how much of it is actually about an ideology involving how to deal with the finances of this country?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's going to be very clear, if people want to play brinkmanship with the debt ceiling and ultimately we are unable to pay our debts or worse unable to make payments to our military, to our Social Security recipients and others, what's going to happen is it's going to send a shockwave to our economy, it's going to drive interest rates up, it's going to cripple businesses all around our country.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Given that state of affairs, it's not in their interest politically to get him out of this hole, is it?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "It's the worst possible time for America to be in this position, isn't it?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "And at the moment, they haven't flexed their muscles in the way that you just discussed involving Suez, but they could do, couldn't they?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Well, to me, it's never about pointing blame.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "Everybody, really, in whatever way big or small has a bit of responsibility for the situation, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I have a lot of faith in the leader that we have in the White House.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "If you were running the country right now and could talk to Americans in a way that perhaps woke them up to reality, what would you say?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "First of all, this is the thing we have to get out of the habit of.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "In a simple way, what is the most effective way that you have seen to get them back to work, or the best plan that you've heard?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Look, you know, the governor, I always joke with him and I consider him a friend.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Would you welcome him doing that?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "It can be pretty serious stuff.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "This is pretty serious stuff, isn't it?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "One thing you need to remember is this: you don't want to wait or depend on this government to manage your life.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "What are your key points of advice for people who look at this and are vaguely terrified?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Well, that's exactly right.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "And is that the key lesson here, that when things look too good to be true, they always are too good to be true?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's the misnomer.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Don't lots of people need to have some form of debt just to function?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Well, I think there's certainly differences between a nation's debt and a personal debt.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Which, in your eyes, in your expert debt is dumb eyes, is normally the best way to get out of a crisis like this?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "The date of the wedding.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Going to reveal the date of the wedding?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110713pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "Can I tell him?", "qSentId": 482}]